a very central wellbeing is the can point when you sound the torch
当您听到火炬声时，最重要的好处就是可以指向
unreliable outside world around two thousand years ago
大约两千年前，外面的世界不可靠
bump bottle for effect on everyone's surfing with bi-polar burdened
颠簸瓶对每个人的冲浪都具有双极负担
and dropdown because the dental care about to many thanks
和下拉列表，因为牙科护理非常感谢
is color gulliver is not to stop karin all together but to care but you're
颜色格列佛不是要一起阻止卡林，而是要关心，但你在
right things and stop clinging to anything that doesn't matter what
正确的事情，不要紧贴任何无关紧要的东西
matters and doesn't matter according to everyone's epic
根据每个人的史诗而重要和无关紧要
is bantu by reality about play century snowball bx in an ever changing
在不断变化的现实中玩弄世纪雪球bx是现实的班图语
environment this reality is effective mix color in it
环境这个现实是有效地在其中混合颜色
die underline tennet office work the die colony court control something's
下划线Tennet办公室工作殖民地法院控制某事
arena control otherwise I would have managed to concern even with the sphinx in it
竞技场控制，否则即使狮身人面像也可以解决
control how jar and position or strict
控制罐子的位置和位置或严格
buttonfreak leaks these things and focus on what are all control
buttonfreak泄漏了这些东西并集中在所有控件上
how your arms position a weakness is specially what you understand was how
您的手臂如何定位弱点特别是您了解的方式
they even look up for life of software the war rosings week link to and twice
他们甚至会寻找战争玫瑰周链接到的软件的寿命，并且两次
it better to login this video explorer the bottle vf effect
最好登录此视频资源管理器瓶vf效果
everyone's and who according to him should focus on to be happy and content
每个人以及根据他的人应该专注于获得快乐和满足
and also letgo shower off and keep your goal
并放开淋浴，保持目标
by the way you find more stories with them in so new book
顺便一提的是，您在新书中发现了更多故事
stoicism for inner peace which contains my collected works on remaining calm and
坚忍内心的和平主义，其中包含我收集的关于保持冷静和冷静的作品
focuses throughout the challenging times of the link in the description
着眼于描述中链接的整个挑战时期
the then my sources of effect everyone's philosophy ark all the discourses and only
然后我的影响力来源每个人的哲学都围绕着所有论述
radium which containers workshop with dan
镭与丹哪个容器车间
written down by people area the change and text can teach as
由人们写下来的变化和文字可以教为
many things about achieving a state of contentment
关于达成满意状态的许多事情
and would execute a European order final fight against outside
并将执行欧洲订单与外界的最后一战
circumstances that would surely experience and third vol
肯定会遇到的情况和第三卷
in the first chapter of discourses everyone's effect makes clear that outside
在第一章中，每个人的影响都表明
circumstances and olie her as even wie let them which is a quick link to then i
情况，甚至连她都不愿让她失望，这是当时我的快速链接
gibson example of going into exile are that b in exiled thousand prevent
吉布森流亡的例子是流亡的b防止了b。
them from going with a smile norm that in cheerful and jerry hall ever
他们从笑容中走出来，在快乐而杰里的大厅里
through it sounded video abby exiled is a great red chili or
通过它听起来流放的艾比视频是一个很棒的红色辣椒或
toe is professions and the people that i had been separated from you love ben in
脚趾是职业，我和你分居的人都爱本
agony effect everyone's new very well that the
痛苦的影响每个人的新感觉都很好
possibility of being exiled it is hours to choose not be cheerful
被流放的可能性是选择不快乐的几个小时
and syria is for that i didn't care about a former and focused on a letter is how
叙利亚是因为我不在乎前者，而专注于一封信是
oil focus on what we can control and let go of everything has done nothing
石油专注于我们可以控制的东西，放手一切都无济于事
outsider for even can harness the question arises what exactly i lie
局外人甚至可以利用问题出现我到底在说谎
zwitterions control and what a thousand here is what effective
两性离子控制和有效千位数在这里是什么有效
cities in the first chapter of the radium only
镭第一章中的城市
and i won samsung sharp control and although not think signal controller
而且我赢得了三星的敏锐控制，虽然没有想到信号控制器
opinion pursuit design already there persian and in a word
一言以蔽之，意见寻求设计已经在那里
whatever aro dantians links modern control
无论aro dantians与现代控制技术有何联系
arbo the property reputation comment and in one when for ipod iphone
arbo物业声誉评论，以及在何时使用ipod iphone
actions and quote so simply put the outside world is not and also control
动作和报价如此简单地把外面的世界也没有，也可以控制
with the way which used to act in and position or even then word the outside
用过去的方式和位置，甚至是外面的话
world is in a control agent effect everyone's thousand encourage
世界在一个控制代理人的作用下，每个人都千载难逢
you to not care about anything alle contrarie live in a good and more i live
你不关心任何事情都生活在一个美好的生活中，我生活得更多
in accordance with nature is a stowbox mangle which slice entirely with a too
符合自然的是一个stowbox mangle，它也完全被切成薄片
cool roll some cheese and carl just doesn't sound to you
凉卷一些奶酪和卡尔只是听起来不对
what snowcontrol picasso that sphinx article week and
狮身人面像文章周的降雪毕加索作品是什么，
reliable yes the enchanting xciting outside world
可靠是迷人的外界
of pleasure sweet bad insatiable who often the
享乐甜蜜坏得了不满足的人经常
interesting enough to pursue zoey design what the world has to offer and cling to
足以进行zoey设计的有趣事物，世界必须提供并坚持
anything that the lights de mind and sense is what losing development two
灯光在意念和感觉上所发生的一切都是失去发展的两个方面
words unfortunately is week one and lewis is
不幸的是，单词是第一周，而刘易斯是
up to four to so epilator have one as deep and anne
最多四到三颗脱毛器，其中一颗和安妮一样深
frank set arm that you were fortune control how i feel
坦率地说，你算命的手臂控制着我的感觉
before that expert someone knew on clinging to stuff that we don't control
在那位专家之前，有人知道坚持使用我们无法控制的东西
if you want to develop as throne and stables and salvo wellbeing
如果您想发展成为宝座，马s和齐备的福祉
luckily epictetus providers with situations and methods to this and for
幸运的是，墓志铭者提供了与此相关的情况和方法
sizing the power of a reason and faculty and the value in the think outside of
评估原因和能力的力量以及外部思考的价值
for this video it f structured these things differently
对于本视频，它以不同的方式构造了这些东西
for the site of usability and based on what is effective bioland de
针对可用性的地点，并基于有效的生物地带
first chapter of the encore radio and th heide stil 3 categories of things that
安可广播的第一章和思想的3个方面
to better stop clinging to recover from porn fell one-stop clinging
更好地停止紧贴从色情中恢复跌落一站式紧贴
to object people and power goodbye pardew me nature not only to be calm
反对人与权力告别，使我自然不但镇定自若
attached to the people you so shared with but also to object how repeatedly
结识与您共享的人，但也反对如何反复
mistake attachment white shirt a process of elements to get for life
错误依恋白衬衫一生必不可少的过程
and so how deeply enjoy the presence of somone of which the or whatever neck and i
因此，如何深深地享受某人或某人和我的脖子的存在
because that work out of my life nyc murdered rodger is that good or too
因为那是我一生中被纽约市谋杀的罗杰（Rodger）所付出的全部努力
software de los of some one before this love even takes place which have a
在这种爱情发生之前，某人的软件de los有一个
theory with chinese clinging to someone or something inblies
中国人固守于某人或某物的理论
the continue your heart that comes mary 16 a possible that ultimately inevitable
继续您的内心，玛丽16最终可能会不可避免
separation from what where a dutch to in some cases de veer of laws of ben
从荷兰人那里分离出来，在某些情况下从本国法律的角度出发
someone who believes that there is ferry life's chances on session
一个相信轮渡生活有机会的人
revolver from preventing separation, so a box full of power the ancient greek
左轮手枪无法防止分离，所以装满力量的盒子是古希腊
flush for rapid yours pointed out that power is a symbol
急速冲动，指出力量是象征
which is the reason why on training power
这就是为什么要训练力量
usually leads to a hunger for power people corrupt it by power heft
通常会导致对权力的渴望，人们会因权势腐败而将其破坏
peanut butter or misery countless times because they didn't want to give it up
花生酱或苦难无数次，因为他们不想放弃
and wanted more which only course stress what the tower
并想要更多，这只会使塔承受什么压力
of power is that never suggests control
力量永远不会暗示控制
power in itself is not enough control meaning that it can be given en sign at
权力本身是不足以控制的，这意味着可以在
any time fighting the a permanent nature of
任何时候都与...的永久性作斗争
existence is the waif the full or how and to live
存在是对完整事物或生活方式的放弃
gardens with nature estofex then do how your master just of
自然estofex的花园，然后做你的主人
even tour transitions what keeps effective there is a simple but
即使是巡回演出，保持有效的方法也很简单，但
profoon piece of advice on how to treat the world that comes to object people
关于如何对待对象人的世界的建议
and power i suggest that led to treat life as a dinner party is anything
和力量，我建议将人生视为晚宴是什么
brother eye view more effective cities the product your hand and take your share
兄弟之眼查看更有效的城市产品，助您一臂之力
with moderation that it suits you then step it is not yet can you want
适度地适合自己，然后步它还不是你想要的
scratch your design or two words it but wait til
刮擦您的设计或两个字，但要等到
the reach you dude is with regard to children to my life to public post to
您花花公子的触角是关于我一生中的孩子，并公开发布给
riches and occasionally fanciulli biography partner or the ghost or the
财富，偶尔还会出现fanciulli传记的搭档，幽灵或
guards and quote i then go down to say that one
警卫和报价，然后我下去说一个
week and i van reject the things which has said before was walnut oil bio
一周，我范拒绝了之前所说的话，核桃油生物
partner ate the feast on the god but as if the empire
伙伴在上帝身上吃了but席，但好像帝国
this point to living comfort mowgli to nature or simply by halflings ar
这指的是向大自然或仅仅由半身人ar居住的舒适mowgli
in dying in conflict the effect was everyone's wants to table is up
在冲突中死去的后果是每个人都想摆桌子
against the pain of love by changing your perceptions of the rings trilogy
通过改变对戒指三部曲的认识来对抗爱的痛苦
instead of thinking that would zandven or that we are entitled to something or to be
而不是认为那将是赞德文或我们有权获得某种东西或被
with someone who could see and race her as a drink
和一个可以看见的人在一起，我们把她当成酒喝
a quote never say anything i have lost at what a free turned it is your child
引用永不说任何话，我失去了什么是自由转身是你的孩子
of eden is [ __ ] is your eyes that she has returned
伊甸园的迟钝是你的眼睛，她已经回来了
is your always drawing know and therefore need
是您一直在绘画的知识，因此需要
that likewise return with this purpose everyone is on batman whatever it is to you
同样的目的，每个人都在蝙蝠侠上，无论对你是什么
could give or signs to take it back though ygritte youtube process takes care
尽管ygritte youtube程序很小心，但还是可以给它或拿回它的迹象
of it what do view it azure to just as trevor earth view hotel and quote when
其中有什么能像特雷弗地球景观酒店那样看待蔚蓝，并在何时报价
single bold effect everyone's view of links is a for
单个粗体效果，每个人对链接的看法都是为了
of the bunch i don't own anything except alternation faculty
在这群人中，除了轮换老师，我什么都不拥有
because of you eternal children mars pauses ar getting
因为你永恒的孩子火星停顿了
then who wouldn't be able to lose that's who those animals just reborn
那么那些人将无法失去的就是那些动物刚刚重生的人
fitz reality better as their soul is a moment of returning what is a towers
让现实变得更好，因为他们的灵魂是回归高塔的时刻
clothing accessories good answer sp for pain so absolutely web utiles
服装配件疼痛的好答案，所以绝对是网络工具
it's no problem to have things and possibly joy the estlanders were able
拥有东西，也许让祖兰人能够感到高兴是没有问题的
to let go of them any time to stop clinging to the job penguins or else
随时放开他们，不再紧紧抓住工作企鹅，否则
oh ham much you care about what others think about as many people mover heaven
哦，火腿，你在乎别人在想些什么，因为很多人在天堂
and earth just to be like my that's the matter
地球就像我一样
sp and so day and age simply not be light
sp，所以白天和年龄根本就不轻
thousand and danger of life's in the majority of cases and you were not
在大多数情况下都有成千上万的生命危险，而您并非
living in the tribal edge anymore one acceptance by the tribe was a major
生活在部落边缘不再是一个部落的接受
of life and death hello for people having a positive in
对生死存亡的人们打招呼
china builds as he since benefits for example and reliable a shirt is him me
中国建立起来是因为他，例如，受益于而可靠的衬衫就是他我
find when effective is sure to final
找出何时有效肯定会最终
romantic partner when sinus martens cable company for more likely to
当窦马尔滕斯电缆公司更可能成为恋人时的浪漫伴侣
higher as the effect is everyone's left and all that
更高，因为效果是每个人都剩下的
outside factors ar inferior two economic systems
外部因素影响两个经济体系
for example that we shouldn't be great one who aren't invited villages
例如我们不应该成为一个不被邀请的村庄的好人
party spf u don't really like the host getting invited to a party concerts
派对SPF你真的不喜欢主持人被邀请参加派对音乐会
cost what you sprees and attendant at were not willing to invest time and energy and
花费了您不愿花时间和精力的东西，并且不愿意花费时间和精力，并且
socialize with a particular person who should be surprised if you don't get
与特定的人交往，如果您不明白，应该感到惊讶
invited to ass party weekend have both ways by not carry on fire
被邀请参加聚会的周末有两种方式不进行射击
who come along to experience the joys of the party what hood your hash and a quote
谁来体验聚会的欢乐，你的哈希表和引号是什么
the night bracing him home you don't like to great
支撑他回家的夜晚，你不喜欢很棒
the launch was behavior at queen just such a snail pretty good guy
发射是在女王的行为，就像这样的蜗牛非常好
word regardless of the pleasure that it
一句话不管它有多高兴
brings about the on-going pursuit of bing liked this exciting
带来了对bing的持续追求，这令人兴奋
racing people i don't want your prize broadcast to social galleries
赛车的人，我不希望您的奖品传播到社交画廊
that we don't because we tent and for what is not for the sake of tranquility '
我们之所以这么做不是因为我们搭帐篷，不是为了安宁而做的事情，
which cannot be achieved in flow is where you build some bieber a lot
在流程中无法实现的是，您在其中建立了更多的能力
furthermore effective said we must be left at rituals and the spiced
更有效的说，我们必须任由礼节和香料
d'este pryce who has to be free for economics then
d'este pryce那时必须自由从事经济学
and tranquility how you must be content to be felt stewart and was to make a speech
与安宁你必须满足于被斯图尔特感动并发表演讲
herself was who she here as not know my other volt
她自己就是她在这里的人，因为我不知道我的另一个伏特
els you it to whether management oil peak edge and whether the d
告诉您管理油峰边缘是否以及
joop pinions of other people arbi alle control what degree to which they effect
其他人的小齿轮Arbi Alle控制着他们影响的程度
if live with an arm control i do link to
如果与手臂控制住，我确实链接到
people sapiens and the letter or even be guided by the or three take some benefit
人们的智慧和信，甚至是由或三个人的指导，都会带来一些好处
weekend of that before i let go for ever to what the plague in all comes down to
在那之前的一个周末，在我永远放弃所有瘟疫归根结底之前
skillfully handling the tool which is an ability to form opinions
熟练地处理工具，可以形成意见
about opinions i will remember that nat i
关于意见，我会记得
who cares a language or a blow insults what the principles which represents the
谁在乎一种语言或一击就侮辱了代表什么的原则
things essence alting because for that anyone profile offers shirt
事情本质上改变了，因为为此，任何人都提供衬衫
third this your own opinion which profile
第三，这是您自己的看法，哪个个人资料
three stop clinging to outcomes and ideas de universis objects that some old mercy
三个停滞不前的结果和思想，反对普遍存在的观点
try to be controls and to lose a free time try to change is and two site a
尝试成为控制者并失去空闲时间尝试改变的是和两个站点
battle weekend win get people often on your byte of what
周末的战斗胜利经常使人们对你的想法感到满意
should have now watch what happens in the boss and be good in the future
现在应该观察老板会发生什么并且将来会变得更好
and the model richard de more life will heart effectively alsace
模特Richardard de more life将有效地阿尔萨斯
holy [ __ ] wicker servant even door servant is expected to be your bigint
神圣的狗屎柳条仆人甚至门仆都有望成为你的大佬
that mix color that is of such important to was the sky should be in his power
对天空如此重要的混合色应该在他的力量中发挥作用
to not always conform to detail dia people are people and it in their nature
并非总是符合细节dia people are people and本质上是人
back then already had bfs which now watch more important
那时已经有了bfs，现在观看更重要
therefore servant is never at the or that the mistress leverages happy weekend and
因此，仆人永远不在，或情妇利用周末快乐，并且
the acceptance that the servant blew a thousand oil sector is the prize du pays for
仆人炸掉一千个石油部门的认可是杜支付的奖品
icon amity we can use this example is a metaphor
图标友善，我们可以使用这个例子是一个隐喻
for anything for example weekend expecto the world to be a
对于任何事情，例如周末期盼世界都将是
offensive science and people who share and some people sites of answer is not
攻击性科学与人共享，而某些人的答案不是
going to change that there will always be someone of vending so beautiful and slim
要改变的是，总会有人贩售这么漂亮又苗条的东西
we have given up arguments so the idea of ​​an offensive world in
我们放弃了争论，所以在...
which you mentor in is unrealistic and a browsing station ideal another
您在其中进行指导是不现实的，而浏览站则是另一个理想选择
problem in the morning then 'code a more useful on red would be to start with
早晨的问题，然后在红色上编码一个更有用的方法是
being more client or self we have control over parents me
作为更多的客户或自我，我们可以控制父母
or may not follow marlie what there is not up to was s i taylor cities it
或可能不追随玛丽，这是我在泰勒城所做的一切
kill that moment a finn got one if you knew what was i have an sd
如果你知道我有一个SD，那杀死一个芬兰人的那一刻
aim annual gowan and great effect iris
瞄准年度高湾和虹膜效果好
emphasizes the weekend control the world with wicam control a rather to two hearts
强调周末用wicam控制世界而不是控制两颗心
it some comments altas some newspaper control
它有一些评论，也有一些报纸控制
wat who sings or feel about this so we can take away your possession of
谁唱歌或感觉到的扫管so，以便我们可以带走您的所有
steel armani it knows control whether or not where the prestabo this like
钢阿玛尼，它知道控制是否像这样的prestabo
pause scan cheetahs of the sap then allowed some degree this
暂停树液的扫描猎豹，然后在一定程度上允许
effect sars the coming and going as if the world i'm not to was
效果使来来往往像我不去的世界一样
how you sound nonetheless you then who does what if i accept and and focus
尽管如此，你的声音你会怎样，如果我接受并集中精力，那该怎么办
on living well despite the wings of fortune who will
依靠命运的翅膀过着幸福的生活，谁会
thank you
谢谢你
[Music]
[音乐]